mylloyd.com 2019-03-26

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is applicable to persons who visit www.mylloyd.com through any online channel/resources like the website; mobile site etc. The applicability of this Privacy Policy also extends to persons who visit the offices or sales channels of www.mylloyd.com.  
The Privacy Policy covers the practices for handling and securing your Personal Information by www. mylloyd.com.  
As a User / Customer of www.mylloyd.com, you agree to abide by the norms mentioned herein. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the websites, mobile sites and mobile apps of our other third parties, even if their websites are linked to www.mylloyd.com website. We recommend you to review the privacy statements of the other parties with whom you interact 

### What personal information or data is collected from you and how we use it?

"Personal Information" means and includes all information collected for lawful purpose and for meeting the objectives of www. mylloyd.com. The information also includes details that can be linked to an individual or to identify any such individual, viz. name, contact number, email address, etc.   
When you visit www.mylloyd.com website, we may collect information regarding the domain name and host from which you are accessing the website, the internet protocol address of the computer / laptop or internet service provider you are using and any other statistical data. The users/customers are informed through this Privacy Policy that www.mylloyd.com uses cookies and tracking technology for website and mobile site users depending on the features offered. Personal information will not be collected via cookies and other tracking technology; however, if you previously provided personal identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. www.mylloyd.com also requests its users/customers to go through the cookies as mentioned below in this Privacy Policy.

### Restriction as to sharing of information

Users / Customers of this website may share contents or information, reviews, comments, send communications; and submit suggestions, ideas, comments, questions or other details, as long as the content is not illegal, obscene, abusive, threatening, defamatory, invasive of privacy, infringing of intellectual property rights of others or otherwise injurious to third parties, or objectionable and does not consist of or contain software viruses, political campaigning, commercial solicitation, chain letters, mass mailings, or any form of "spam".  
Users / Customers are also restricted to upload any explicit contents which are not acceptable to the public at general and are injurious to the minds of children.

### Surveys and Competitions

From time to time, our site may request information from users via surveys or competitions. Participation in these surveys or competitions is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and address) and demographic information (such as gender, age). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and to award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the functionality and user satisfaction of this site. We do not share aggregated demographic information with our partners or advertisers.

### Registration

If you choose to become a registered member/user/customer of www.mylloyd.com, you must provide us with your name, contact number, e-mail address etc. This information is collected on the registration form for several reasons which are following:

  * To allow us to contact you for customer services, if necessary.
  * To make our services easily available to you.
  * To confirm your new registration and each shopping or Purchase you make.
  * This information is used to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest.

### Procedure for Collection of Information and its Use

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this website www.mylloyd.com. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily provide us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.  
We will use the information provided by you to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, unless required by government or statutory authority or regulatory offices under the law.  
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to inform you about the up comings promotional offers or new services, or changes to this privacy policy.

### Your access to the information provided by you

  * You may choose to visit our site at any time to check or review or revise the following information or data provided by you by contacting us via email or customer helpline number given on our website www.mylloyd.com.
  * See what data we have about you, if any.
  * Change/correct any data we have about you.
  * Have us delete any data we have about you.
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

### Security

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secured way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.  
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, invoicing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

### Cookies

We use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.

### Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information. 

### Updates

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page. With whom is your personal information shared? We do not share customer information collected on the website with anybody. Havells India Limited is the sole user of such information, and this information is used to contact the users for further promotions and sharing product-related information only. We review our Privacy Policy from time to time, and we may make periodic changes to the policy in connection with that review. Therefore, you may wish to bookmark this page and/or periodically review this page to make sure you have the latest version. You may always submit concerns regarding this Privacy Policy via email to support@lloydmail.com and we will respond to all reasonable concerns or inquiries. 

### Thank you for using the Website!
